Question: am i going to win?
Response: {'question': 'am i going to win?', 'answer': 'You may rely on it', 'type': 'positive'}

Question: is it going to rain?
Response: {'question': 'is it going to rain?', 'answer': 'Yes, definitely', 'type': 'positive'}

Question: is my sister mad?
Response: {'question': 'is my sister mad?', 'answer': 'Yes, definitely', 'type': 'positive'}

Question: does she have a brain?
Response: {'question': 'does she have a brain?', 'answer': 'Very doubtful', 'type': 'negative'}

Question: does she have a brain
Response: {'question': 'does she have a brain', 'answer': 'Reply hazy, try again', 'type': 'neutral'}

Question: does she have a brain
Response: {'question': 'does she have a brain', 'answer': 'You may rely on it', 'type': 'positive'}

Question: what
Response: {'question': 'what', 'answer': 'Without a doubt', 'type': 'positive'}

Question: does swami love me
Response: {'question': 'does swami love me', 'answer': 'Don’t count on it', 'type': 'negative'}

Question: is my sister mad?
Response: {'question': 'is my sister mad?', 'answer': 'Don’t count on it', 'type': 'negative'}

Question: is my sister mad?
Response: {'question': 'is my sister mad?', 'answer': 'You may rely on it', 'type': 'positive'}

Question: does swami loves shireesha
Response: {'question': 'does swami loves shireesha', 'answer': 'My reply is no', 'type': 'negative'}

Question: does swami loves prashanthi
Response: {'question': 'does swami loves prashanthi', 'answer': 'You may rely on it', 'type': 'positive'}

Question: does swami loves pranitha
Response: {'question': 'does swami loves pranitha', 'answer': 'Reply hazy, try again', 'type': 'neutral'}

Question: does swami loves upender
Response: {'question': 'does swami loves upender', 'answer': 'Yes, definitely', 'type': 'positive'}

Question: please swami love me
Response: {'question': 'please swami love me', 'answer': 'Very doubtful', 'type': 'negative'}

Question: does swami love shireesha 
Response: {'question': 'does swami love shireesha ', 'answer': 'Reply hazy, try again', 'type': 'neutral'}

Question: does swami loves prashanthi
Response: {'question': 'does swami loves prashanthi', 'answer': 'My reply is no', 'type': 'negative'}

Question: does swami loves prashanthi
Response: {'question': 'does swami loves prashanthi', 'answer': 'Very doubtful', 'type': 'negative'}


